<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Xidan Chen</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Xidan Chen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Chi-Square Difference Testing Using the Satorra-Bentler Scaled Chi-Square with Results from Mplus</title>
      <link>/2018/11/07/chi-square-difference-testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/11/07/chi-square-difference-testing/</guid>
      <description>I was working on a project for which I need to run around 50 sets of comparisons of nested models. For the non-normal continuous data I was working with, I used the MLR as estimation method. Mplus unfortunately won’t compute the chi-square difference test using MLR chi-square. Following their guide here http://www.statmodel.com/chidiff.shtml, I therefore wrote these functions to automate my analysis. Although these functions were written for my own analysis using MLR, the same functions could also be used for MLM (Satorra-Bentler) and WLSM chi-square.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A quick step-by-step guide to build your own website using Blogdown, Github, Netlify</title>
      <link>/2018/11/05/build-website-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/11/05/build-website-r/</guid>
      <description>If you are interested in creating your own website through RStudio, but don’t want to spend time reading the book blogdown: Creating Websites with R Markdown, and have no idea about version control, data managment, etc. Here is the step-by-step guide for you:
STEP1:First, log into your github account, creat a new repository. If you don’t have github account, create one.
click the + sign at the upper-right corner of the panel</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cognitive impairment</title>
      <link>/2018/11/04/cognitive-impairment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/11/04/cognitive-impairment/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>packages</title>
      <link>/projects/packages/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/packages/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a scientist&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>